# ONIFADE RIDWAN

### BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER



- +2349032516338
- ridwanonifadeicus@gmail.com
- No 1,Onikiola Street,Iberekodo,Abeokua,Ogun .
- icus101.github.io/portfoliowebsite

## **PROFILE**

I am a self-taught full stack blockchain developer and a web developer with 2 years of experience in writing Solana smart contracts and website design. I can also create tokens and NFTs on the Solana blockchain. Team player with an eye for detail.

## SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Typescript
- Rust
- Next JS
- Tailwind CSS
- Solidity
- Anchor

## EDUCATION

#### SECONDARY SCHOOL

Command Day Secondary School **2010 - 2013** 

#### **BACHELOR OF MEDICINE**

Obafemi Awolowo University 2017- 2023

## EXPERIENCE

#### **APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER**

Really Great Company

2019 - Present

- Freelancer on Fiver and upwork
- Built spl Tokens and NFTs
- Created Candy machine with frontend integration

#### SECONDARY SCHOOL TEACHER

Really Great Company 2016-2019

• A good Physics and Chemistry teacher

#### PRIMARY SCHOOL TEACHER

Really Great Company 2014-2016

• A good science primary school teacher.